<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Truepool.io</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Truepool.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 17:26:48 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to use Chia on TrueNAS</title>
      <link>/kb/how-to-use-chia-on-truenas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 17:26:48 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kb/how-to-use-chia-on-truenas/</guid>
      <description>How to use Chia on TrueNAS  TrueNAS SCALE 21.08 The preferred method of running Chia on TrueNAS is to use the containerized application on TrueNAS SCALE 21.06 and later.
Chia is available as an app in the official TrueNAS SCALE Applications repository
Setup of Chia on TrueNAS scale is very straight-forward.
 Navigate to the &amp;ldquo;Apps&amp;rdquo; section Locate Chia and click install Give the application a name, I.E. chia1 Review the other pages, and click &amp;ldquo;Submit&amp;rdquo; when finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Truepool</title>
      <link>/pages/join-truepool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/join-truepool/</guid>
      <description>Why Truepool?  Truepool is unique in that it is one of the only pools run by a team of experienced Crypto and Open Source storage experts, that actively contributes back to Open Source development.
25% of all XCH operator fees are donated back to the TrueNAS project, to support its continuted growth and success as the world&amp;rsquo;s #1 software defined storage system.
Following it&amp;rsquo;s open-source ethos, Truepool strives to run and manage itself in the best spirit of open source collaboration, by providing docker images and other helpful resources to prospective Chia farmers running TrueNAS CORE and SCALE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaderboard</title>
      <link>/pages/leaderboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/leaderboard/</guid>
      <description>  Rank Points ID   Loading...     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TruePool Docker Image</title>
      <link>/kb/truepool-docker-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kb/truepool-docker-image/</guid>
      <description>TruePool Docker Image  What is it? To assist our Chia farmers, TruePool.io is pleased to make available a customized docker image which includes the official chia client, as well as a handful of helpful tools for serious farmers.
This image is used as the basis of the official TrueNAS Plugin for TrueNAS SCALE, but can be used by anybody with the ability to run containers.
The image includes the following:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
